hi i'm charles martin and i'm a lecturer
in the anu school of computing
welcome to comp 1720-6720
art and interaction computing now this
is a course where you'll learn to create
expressive art with computer code
you'll use code to paint to draw to
compose and sketch
more importantly you'll make artworks
that are interactive they'll respond to
the viewer using the keyboard
mouse camera and microphone on your
computer
we're going to talk about the qualities
of computer-based art and about what it
means for an artwork to be interactive
you'll learn the coding or programming
skills that you'll need to create
interactive artworks
and you'll be able to design and create
a major artistic project
and display it in our online gallery now
this is an introductory course
you're not required to have any previous
coding or artistic experience
our team will teach you everything you
need to know from the ground up
if this is your first time coding
welcome you're about to start on an
exciting journey
and if you don't feel that you're very
artistic you're welcome too
once you get started you might surprise
yourself the lectures and labs for comp
are all available on our website right
now this year we'll be having online
lectures and a mix of online and
in-person labs
every week i'll be bringing streaming
lectures to you online
on teams on youtube or on twitch whether
you're here in canberra or joining us
online you're very welcome
i'm really looking forward to getting
started and to seeing the kinds of
interactive art that you make